Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/razi-tavakoli (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Data Analysis
Programming

Razi Tavakoli, Ph.D.

Data Scientist

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Experience in Data analytical and Programming skills specialized in coding Python, C++

Experience with Deep Neural Networks, Machine Learning (Keras and TensorFlow), R, SAS

Experience with Natural Language Processing NLP (NLTK) Involved in Data gathering, manipulation, synthesis, modeling, and communication of insights

Specialized in Analytical and Numerical Statistical Analysis Experience with Data Visualization using Tableau

Experience

The University of Texas at Arlington
Data Scientist
October 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 6 months)
Arlington, Texas

BlueWater Solutions Group, Inc.
Data Analyst
May 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 5 months)
Lawrence, Kansas Area

I worked as data analyst and my responsibilities were including data collection, data preprocessing and analyzing data using supervised and unsupervised machine learning algorithms. I have also used different tools for data visualization including Tableau.

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Engineering · (2015 - 2018)